statement researchers would say no no
we're only working on machine learning
because working on AI was seen as way too out there
in 2010 just the very mention of the phrase AGI
artificial general intelligence
would get you some seriously strange looks
and even a cold shoulder
you're actually building AGI people would say
isn't that something out of science fiction
people thought it was 50 years away or 100 years away
if it was even possible
at all talk of AI was I guess kind of embarrassing
people generally thought we were weird
I guess in some ways we kind of were
it wasn't long though
before AI
started beating humans at a whole range of tasks
that people previously thought were way out of reach
understanding images
translating languages transcribing